unixmen.com 2014-11-21

# Privacy Policy | Unixmen

Share this Article: 000000

All content and materials published within the Unixmen network and its associated entities is published and released under the **Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NonDerivs 3.0 Unported License (CC BY-NC-ND 3.0)**. For exact details and specifications of this license, please visit <http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-nd/3.0>

In addition to the aforementioned license, content/materials published within the Unixmen network and its associated entities is published under mutual agreement with our Freelance Staff Writers, who also hold individual ownership over the content posted with their name associated and/or attached as Author or any other authoritative association to that specific content/material.  
If you should have any questions regarding legalities of any content/materials published within the Unixmen network and its associated entities, please email our independent Legal Representatives at webmaster@unixmen.com

At Unixmen, our Staff Writers try to test the applications we write about and recommend. In some cases, we may not be able to test the application as much as we like. In such a case, we can’t be held liable/responsible for any loss/damage/discomfort occurred as a result of using an application or product we’ve written about or recommended.

Any personal information you provide to us including and/or similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, shared or leased to any entities or individuals outside of the Unixmen network.

Unixmen is not responsible for the content of external internet sites which are either linked or recommended by us. You are advised to read the Privacy Policy of any external sites before disclosing any personal information to all external parties outside of Unixmen.

A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and possibly on your computer’s hard drive. This allows any website on the Unixmen network to recognize you each time you visit one of our websites. Cookies do not contain any personal information. Our website utilizes 3rd parties who employ browser cookies and other technologies to collect information about users, such as IP address, type of web browser used, web pages viewed and other information. We take measures to ensure that our cookies do not collect personally identifiable or sensitive information. The information we collect within the Unixmen network is analyzed and may be combined with similar information of other visitors to our website. You may set your browser to reject cookies. However, this can affect some functions of Unixmen.com.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve advertising components based on a user’s prior visits to Unixmen. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables Google and its partners to serve advertising to you based on your visit to Unixmen and/or other sites on the internet. If you want to opt out of the use of the DART cookie, please visit the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

0 people like this
